[{"answer": "I think it is inappropriate measure, I feel horrible for, you know, kids that are not involved, what I mean -- we are a small town, I mean things like shouldn't happen in a small community like ours.", "docId": "131120pmt", "aSentId": 19, "question": "ORGAN: How do you feel about the punishment in terms of the fact the whole town now will have to football, do you think it is an appropriate measure to have been taken?", "qSentId": 18}, {"answer": "He's cleats were taken out of his locker, water were put on them and they were put in the trash.", "docId": "131120pmt", "aSentId": 31, "question": "What kind of thing has been going on?", "qSentId": 30}, {"answer": "What's that, I'm sorry.", "docId": "131120pmt", "aSentId": 34, "question": "And Anthony Phillips, has he been subjected to other racist abuse?", "qSentId": 33}, {"answer": "No, no this was the first incident that ever that word has been used towards my son.", "docId": "131120pmt", "aSentId": 36, "question": "I'm sorry, yes, I was just asking you, if he been subjected to other racist abuse, other than the graffiti?", "qSentId": 35}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, what people fail to say to each other, I mean I guess that's, you know, that's your right.", "docId": "131120pmt", "aSentId": 43, "question": "I made the point that, you know, if you're going to have rap stars and other leading figures in the black community using that word in songs and everything else, what kind of message does that send to the youth of America?", "qSentId": 42}, {"answer": "No, he does not.", "docId": "131120pmt", "aSentId": 51, "question": "And Andrea, do you think that Isaac knows who sprayed this graffiti?", "qSentId": 50}, {"answer": "I don't think it's labeling them as quitters at all by doing that.", "docId": "131120pmt", "aSentId": 77, "question": "What is your opinion?", "qSentId": 76}, {"answer": "Well, yes, you know, that, you know, he would be -- I mean that he would love to be playing.", "docId": "131120pmt", "aSentId": 85, "question": "Does he just want it get it sorted as quickly as possible?", "qSentId": 84}, {"answer": "Uptight is not the word.", "docId": "131120pmt", "aSentId": 125, "question": "Why was A-Rod so uptight about everything?", "qSentId": 124}, {"answer": "He hates my guts.", "docId": "131120pmt", "aSentId": 136, "question": "Does he like you?", "qSentId": 135}, {"answer": "Well, honestly, I have no idea.", "docId": "131120pmt", "aSentId": 145, "question": "Why there's so many think that he's just another Lance Armstrong in the making?", "qSentId": 144}, {"answer": "There's not a human being with a brain that has a motivation to go against Alex that thinks everyone else gets 50 and Alex gets 211 and that's normal.", "docId": "131120pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "Are you simply enraged by what you view as (inaudible)?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "As a matter of fact -- well, Alex has admitted that.", "docId": "131120pmt", "aSentId": 178, "question": "When was the last time took, you know?", "qSentId": 177}, {"answer": "I absolutely believe him, because I've seen the evidence and it would defy science.", "docId": "131120pmt", "aSentId": 183, "question": "Alex Rodriguez says and you believe him that he's not taking performance-enhancing drugs for at least a decade?", "qSentId": 182}, {"answer": "Well, Piers in my honest opinion and I'm not medical doctor, but I believed that George is suffering from untreated post traumatic stress disorder.", "docId": "131120pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "What is your reaction to this latest incident involving your friend George Zimmerman, given it's now the fourth time I think that he's been involved in such a clash with the police?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "... always been around ...", "docId": "131120pmt", "aSentId": 218, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 217}, {"answer": "You know, you know, what ...", "docId": "131120pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "And someone knows slogan?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "I'm just asking you this.", "docId": "131120pmt", "aSentId": 276, "question": "You want to hear the facts?", "qSentId": 275}, {"answer": "How many -- My point was you said as his friend, he's suffering from a mental illness, post traumatic stress disorder.", "docId": "131120pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "Is it say right to bear arm in it?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "He killed unarmed teenager.", "docId": "131120pmt", "aSentId": 320, "question": "He's on his way out to target and next thing you know, he's living his life on the run and he's got quite a few people after him, OK, because they believe that he murdered as you call it unarmed teenager, OK?", "qSentId": 319}, {"answer": "Well, I'm increasingly aware that there must be a correlation between his mental condition and his propensity to threaten women with guns, yes, because that seems to be a pattern with every woman that he comes across.", "docId": "131120pmt", "aSentId": 333, "question": "Are you aware of that?", "qSentId": 332}, {"answer": "Absolutely appalled, but Piers, I think there were some hints of what his possible defense maybe if as his prosecution proceeds involving the alleged victim Samantha, his girlfriend.", "docId": "131120pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "I mean, what do you make of that?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "... that would help the defense ...", "docId": "131120pmt", "aSentId": 366, "question": "What about his wife?", "qSentId": 365}, {"answer": "Well -- but I mean according to his friend that appears to be the point of view that is at least his friend has.", "docId": "131120pmt", "aSentId": 371, "question": "Are they all opportunists?", "qSentId": 370}, {"answer": "That doesn't worry me.", "docId": "131120pmt", "aSentId": 397, "question": "Does that worry you?", "qSentId": 396}, {"answer": "Well, obviously many of us like myself warned about the problems we're seeing with ObamaCare and not just with the rollout but with the program itself.", "docId": "131120pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "Are we now in a position where the Republicans would love Kathleen Sebelius to keep her job for as a long as humanly possible?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "Oh, I think any of the 30 Republican Governors are and I think they prove it in the states.", "docId": "131120pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "If somebody like you electable to the Republican Party as their nominee?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "131120pmt", "aSentId": 501, "question": "What was your mind telling you?", "qSentId": 500}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "131120pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "At what point did you realized what have actually happened and how did your parents deal with protecting you as the fact, you're so young?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "131120pmt", "aSentId": 514, "question": "Is there a day, Jeff Franzen, when you don't think about that day back in Dallas in '63?", "qSentId": 513}, {"answer": "Would've been very different, principally because I think based on the evidence, not wishful thinking, not some gassy (ph) hope that he probably would not have gone into Vietnam.", "docId": "131120pmt", "aSentId": 524, "question": "What was your conclusion?", "qSentId": 523}, {"answer": "This was the darker side.", "docId": "131120pmt", "aSentId": 543, "question": "How would he have dealt with that as a serving president?", "qSentId": 542}, {"answer": "I think it would be less (inaudible).", "docId": "131120pmt", "aSentId": 561, "question": "Would you've been like Johnson, very proactive, or would've been a bit wary, do you think?", "qSentId": 560}, {"answer": "It's very hard to cut through what the death meant and how that put him in a different category, I think he would have been seen by historians as a reasonably successfully president and avoiding World War III gets -- that's a lot of points for me.", "docId": "131120pmt", "aSentId": 569, "question": "Would he have become a truly great president, do you think?", "qSentId": 568}]